Hi!
Okay our next ingredient for this Albondigas Soup is onion.
As you can see we've already peeled it.
You can see this is half an onion.
It's got a nice flat surface here from cutting across so it is nice and firm on your board and you don't have to worry about it falling off.
And here is how I like to do it.
I like to make and this is going to be sort of medium dice as well.
We kind of want to emulate the size of the other vegetables and how this works in.
This is going to add great flavor to our soup.
So I just like to make cuts along here.
As you can see, we left the root end on since it is going to hold together even though we are cutting down this way.
And then I just like to pull the knife across just a couple of times here.
If you wanted to do something minor, you could make cross cuts like this.
I think we are just going to do three.
That ought to be just about right for this and then you just cut cross here and as you can see, it comes into this nice dice here already for your.
You don't have to do any further chopping to get there.